A Guide to the Secretary of the Board of Visitors, Office Administrative Files [1966]-1988
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Secretary of the Board of Visitors, Office Administrative Files [1966]-1988
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-1/2/1.901
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
For ten years from the date of creation, access to these records will be granted only under the procedures of the Virginia Freedom of Information Act (Code of Virginia -2.1-340 ff.) or with the specific permission of the Secretary of the Board. Researchers interested in obtaining access to these records should direct a request in writing to the Office of the Legal Adviser, Madison Hall, University of Virginia.
Acquisition Information
This collection was transferred to the library on 1990 July 12.
Contents List
- Admissions 1980-1988 (Box 1)
- Board Meetings 1985-1988, 3 folders (Box 1)
- Board of Visitors-Memoranda 1987, 2 folders (Box 1)
- Board of Visitors-Memoranda 1988, 3 folders (Box 2)
- Budget 1984-1987, 2 folders (Box 2)
- Clinch Valley College 1967-1985 (Box 2)
- College of Arts and Sciences 1978-1983, 1 of 2 (Box 2)
- Consent Forms Re Replacement Resolution on Interim Financing 1982-1983, 2 of 2 (Box 2)
- Consent Forms Re Replacement Resolution on Interim Financing 1982-1983 (Box 3)
- Continuing Education, School of 1970-1983 (Box 3)
- Decals-Board of Visitors 1976-1972 (Box 3)
- Endowment Funds 1971-1986 (Box 3)
- Executive Vice President 1976-1981 (Box 3)
- Faculty 1971 (Box 3)
- Faculty Housing 1972-1978 (Box 3)
- Fee, Comprehensive 1969-1976 (Box 3)
- Fee, Student Activities 1970-1973 (Box 3)
- Fees 1968-1975 (Box 3)
- Honor System 1970-1985, 2 folders (Box 3)
- Honor Loan Fund 1985 (Box 4)
- Named Professorships and Endowment Chairs 1966-1988, 5 folders (Box 4)
- Tuition 1970-1972 (Box 4)